Guide to the Metropolitan Cooperative Milk Producers Bargaining Agency records, 1932-1958.
Metropolitan Cooperative Milk Producers Bargaining Agency records, 1932-1958.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Metropolitan Cooperative Milk Producers Bargaining Agency records, 1932-1958.
1899
Metropolitan Cooperative Milk Producers Bargaining Agency.
8 v.; .1 cubic ft.
Scrapbooks, clippings, and other printed items.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Scrapbooks, clippings, and other printed items pertaining to milk marketing, pricing, and control, strikes, the appointment of Charles H. Baldwin as New York State Commissioner of Agriculture and Markets, and other material concerning the dairy industry, including a scrapbook of clippings on the New York State Fair and various county fairs.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Scrapbooks, clippings, and other printed items pertaining to milk marketing, pricing, and control, strikes, the appointment of Charles H. Baldwin as New York State Commissioner of Agriculture and Markets, and other material concerning the dairy industry, including a scrapbook of clippings on the New York State Fair and various county fairs.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Metropolitan Cooperative Milk Producers Bargaining Agency.; Baldwin, Charles H.; New York State. Department of Agriculture.
Subjects:
Milk trade--New York (State); Dairying--New York (State); Strikes and lockouts--New York (State); Fairs--New York (State)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Newspaper clippings on the subject of milk control, Aug. 6, 1934-Feb. 5, 1935 (Volume 8)
- Newspaper clippings on milk control, Aug. 13, 1933-Mar. 22, 1934 (Volume 6)
- Miscellaneous newspaper clippings re: milk control, pricing and milk strikes etc., Apr.-Aug. 1933 (Volume 5)
- Newspaper clippings on milk control, Mar. 23-Aug. 4, 1934 (Volume 7)
- Newspaper clippings - State and County Fairs (N.Y.S. Fair at Syracuse, 1932-1934; Albany, Chenango, Delaware, and Wyoming Co. Fairs, 1934) (Volume 1)
- Miscellaneous newspaper clippings on milk marketing, Mr. Baldwin's appointment as Commissioner of Agriculture and Markets, July 1932 (Volume 3)
- Newspaper clippings - miscellaneous information interesting to dairy farmers, Dec. 1932-Feb. 1935 (Volume 4)
- Newspaper clippings on Markets - food control - plant industry - animal industry - state institutions - weights and measures - consumers' information - dog license, 1932-1934 (Volume 2)
- The Metropolitan Milk Producers' News, XVIII, 5 - contains news accounts and editorial on death of Charles H. Baldwin, May 1958 (Box 1)
- Book [royal blue cover with gold lettering], Metropolitan Cooperative Milk Producers' Bargaining Agency, Inc. Contains introduction by Baldwin, Executive Secy. Is devoted largely (p. 16 ff.) to articles on delegates with photographs of them, their houses, and their barns. 191 pp. + map (foldout) of NYS showing locations of the 77 cooperative members; names listed on back of map. Printed by the Corse Press, Sandy Creek, N.Y., 1957 (Box 1)
- Charles H. Baldwin, "The Leadership Training School of the Metropolitan Cooperative Milk Producers Bargaining Agency, Inc." 10 pp., [1957?] (Box 1)
- L.L. Clough, "Fundamental Truths Taught by The New York State Milk Pricing Experiment - and - Services and Protection Rendered by the Division of Milk Control." 29 pp., 1957 (Box 1)
- Charles W. Holman, "The Cooperative Way Wins in America." 89 pp., 1957 (Box 1)
- Ernest C. Strobeck, "The Development of Cooperative Milk Marketing in the New York Milkshed." 44 pp., 1957 (Box 1)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Origin and Development of the Dairymen's League by R.D. Cooper - microfilmed and added to R.D. Cooper papers, #1726.